(siren wailing)
("Bleeding Love" by Leona Lewis)
♪ Closed off from love
I didn't need the pain ♪
♪ Once or twice was enough
and it was all in vain ♪
♪ Time starts to pass before
you know it you're frozen ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ But something happened for
the very first time with you ♪
♪ My heart melts into the
ground found something true ♪
♪ And everyone's looking 'round
thinking I'm going crazy ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ But I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
♪ They try to pull me away but
they don't know the truth ♪
♪ My heart's crippled by the
vein that I keep on closing ♪
♪ You cut me open and I ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ I keep bleeding I keep
keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ You cut me open ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Trying hard not to hear
but they talk so loud ♪
♪ Their piercing sounds fill my ears ♪
♪ Try to fill me with doubt ♪
♪ Yet I know that their goal
is to keep me from falling ♪
♪ Hey oh ♪
♪ But nothing's greater than the rush ♪
♪ That comes with your embrace ♪
♪ And in this world of
loneliness I see your face ♪
♪ Yet everyone around me
thinks that I'm going crazy ♪
♪ Maybe maybe ♪
♪ But I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
♪ They try to pull me away but
they don't know the truth ♪
♪ My heart's crippled by the
vein that I keep on closing ♪
♪ You cut me open and I ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ I keep bleeding I keep
keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ You cut me open ♪
♪ And it's draining all of me ♪
♪ Though they find it hard to believe ♪
♪ I'll be wearing these
scars for everyone to see ♪
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
♪ They try to pull me away but
they don't know the truth ♪
♪ My heart's crippled by the
vein that I keep on closing ♪
♪ Oh you cut me open and I ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ I keep bleeding I keep
keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Oh you cut me open and I ♪
♪ I keep bleeding I keep
keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Keep bleeding keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ Oh you cut me open and I ♪